Guide to the Berkeley Divinity School Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Faculty Staff, Series III
  - Faculty Files
    - Johnson, John (1965-1970), 1962-1971 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Jones, Harry (1966-1971), 1966-1979 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Kalter, Richard (1958-1971) (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - King, Virginia, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Leavy, Stanley (1950-1958), 1950-1971 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - McDaniel, Charlotte Kaseman (1974-1980) (Box 18, Folder 42-43)
    - Mount, William (1962-1970), 1962-1974 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Myers, C. Kilmer (1940-1943), 1941-1970 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Noyce, Gay, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Parachini, David, 1987-1988 Nov (Box 18, Folder 47-49)
    - Rode, Werner (1958-1976), 1957-1980 (Box 18, Folder 50-52)
    - Rodie, Robert (1962-1966?), 1957-1971 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Rowthorn, Jeffery (1973-1987) (Box 19, Folder 54-55)
    - Ruef, John (1960-1971), 1958-1976 (Box 19, Folder 56-57)
  - Faculty Considered, Not Hired
    - Anderson, John, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Mercer, Samuel, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Skinner, John, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Woverton, Wallace, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Faculty Searches
    - Anglican Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Black Faculty, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Continuing Education, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Church History, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Field Education, 1973-1982 (Box 19, Folder 66-67)
    - Pastoral Theology, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Guest Faculty
    - Aagaard, Anna Marie (1975 Spring), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Archdall, H.K. (1954-1957), 1946-1966 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Baker, Albert (1934 Spring), 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Barr, O. Sydney (1959 Fall), 1958-1966 (Box 19, Folder 71b)
    - Barton, Arthur (declined), 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Beevor, Humphrey (1935 Spring), 1934-1946 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Blagrave, R.C. (1929 Spring) (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Briggs, George (1950 Spring), 1948-1960 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Butterworth, George (1935 Fall), 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Carpenter, S.C. (1927 Spring), 1926-1949 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Chase, George (1952 Fall), 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Davey, T.A.E. (1931 Spring), 1930-1945 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Demant, Vigo (1946 Fall), 1943-1956 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Dewar, Lindsay (1932 Fall) (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Duncan-Jones, A.S. (1926 Spring), 1925-1949 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Dwelly, F.W. (1924 Fall), 1924-1925 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Gorton, Neville (1939 Spring), 1938-1951 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - Hall, Herbert W. (1954 Spring), 1952-1955 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Havard, William T. (1951 Fall), 1950-1961 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - Hebert, A. Gabriel (1948 Fall), 1947-1961 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - Hettlinger, Richard F. (1959-1960), 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Hodges, Evelyn Charles (1954 Fall), 1951-1957 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - Hudson, Cyril S. (1927-1948), 1924-1957 (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Knight-Bruce, Ethelfloed (1925 Spring) (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Knox, John (1948 Spring), 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Lewis, C.S. (declined), 1948 (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Mascall, Eric (1958 Spring), 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Mitchell, Lionel (1969-1970), 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - Nash, Arnold (1939 Fall), 1938-1941 (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - Nineham, Dennis E. (1963 Fall), 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 97)
    - O'Driscoll, Herbert (1982 Fall), 1982-1984s (Box 20, Folder 97b)
    - Pym, T.W. (1923 Spring), 1922-1952 (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Ramsey, Michael (declined), 1929-1951 (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - Rice, Otis (1958 Spring) (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Richardson, Alan (1949 Fall), 1948-1953 (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Rogers, Clement F. (1936 Fall), 1936-1948 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - Shepherd, Massey (1941-1947), 1941-1954 (Box 20, Folder 103)
    - Studdert-Kennedy, Geoffrey (1923-1924), 1923-1966 (Box 20, Folder 104)
    - Wand, J. William (1957 Fall), 1955-1958 (Box 20, Folder 105)
    - Wynn, Harold Edward (1950 Fall), 1948-1957 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1922-1953 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - List of Guest Faculty, 1918-1942 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - YDS Faculty
    - Johnson, Robert (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - Kelsey, David (Box 20, Folder 110)
    - Nouwen, Henri, 1971-1981 (Box 20, Folder 111-112)
  - Appointments and Resignations
    - 1-Year Appointments, 1967-1983 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1970 (Box 20, Folder 114)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 115)
    - Around the Merger, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    - Lists of Faculty, 1954-1964 (Box 20, Folder 117)
    - Faculty Evaluations, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Episcopal Faculty
    - Lists of Faculty, 1973-1980 (Box 20, Folder 119)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1983 (Box 20, Folder 120-121)
  - Miscellaneous (Faculty)
    - Sabbaticals, 1961-1981 (Box 20, Folder 122)
    - Salary Comparisons, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 123)
    - Writings: Porter, H. Boone Jr., Spurrier, William, 1955,1963 (Box 20, Folder 124-125)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1971-1975 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - Job Search: Dean of Devel. Church Relations, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    - Endowed Chairs: Goddard Chair in Pastoral Theology (Box 20, Folder 128)
    - Endowed Chairs: Walter Gray Chair in Anglican Studies (Box 20, Folder 129)
    - YDS Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - YDS Faculty Meetings
    - Minutes and Materials, 1971-1982 (Box 21, Folder 131-137)
    - Fall Faculty Conference, 1971, 1974, 1975, 1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 138)
  - BDS Faculty Meetings
    - Minutes Book, 1899-1937 (Box 21)
    - Minutes Book Inserts, 1903-1930 (Box 21, Folder 139)
    - Minutes Books, 1937-1971 (Box 21)
    - Minutes Notebooks, 1964-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 140-141)
    - Minutes and Materials, 1968-1984 (Box 22, Folder 142-148)
  - Staff Files
    - Baxter, T. Chester (Box 22, Folder 149)
    - Jahnige, Lewis P. (Box 22, Folder 150)
    - Noda, Risaburo (Box 22, Folder 151)
    - Raftery-Crawford, Elizabeth, 1947-1986 (Box 22, Folder 152-154)
    - Rogers, Charles A., 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 155)
    - Sulavik, Stephen, 1932-1971 (Box 22, Folder 156)
  - Staff Meetings
    - Materials and Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 22, Folder 157-161)
  - Miscellaneous (Staff)
    - Financial Aid Committee (Box 22, Folder 162)
    - Connecticut Unemployment Law (Box 22, Folder 163)
    - Pension/Benefits, 1948-1956 (Box 22, Folder 164-167)
    - Death Notices, 1957-1986 (Box 22, Folder 168)
- Students, Series IV
  Scope and Contents
  Student files can be consulted only by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School
  Conditions Governing Access
  Student files are restricted until 75 years after last known date of attendance.
  - Students, 2000-2004
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2079, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1990-1999
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2074, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1980-1989
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2064, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1970-1979
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2054, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1960-1969
    Restricted until Jan. 1., 2044, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1950-1959
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2034, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1940-1949
    Restricted until Jan. 1, 2024, except by permission of the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
  - Students, 1930-1939
    Student files can be viewed only with written permission from the Dean of Berkeley Divinity School.
    - Matriculated Students
      - Allen, Charles R., 1938 (Box 51, Folder 1320)
      - Blaney, A. Edward, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 1321)
      - Brown, W. Don (Box 51, Folder 1322)
      - Carroll, Newton L., 1938 (Box 51, Folder 1323)
      - Chater, Edward W., 1938 (Box 51, Folder 1324)
      - Diehl, John R., 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1325)
      - Gosnell, Harold C., 1931 (Box 51, Folder 1326)
      - Hampshire, W. Robert, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 1327)
      - Jacobson, James H., 1934 (Box 51, Folder 1328)
      - Ketchum, Bradford W., 1938 (Box 51, Folder 1329)
      - Linder, Newll D., 1934 (Box 58, Folder 107)
      - Lorentzen, Frederic L., 1932 (Box 59, Folder 116)
      - Loveland, Clara O., 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1330)
      - Luisa, Louis A., 1931 (Box 59, Folder 119)
      - Manderbach, Aaron, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 1331)
      - McGarvey, John P., 1938 (Box 59, Folder 137)
      - Merrill, Edward R. (Box 51, Folder 1332)
      - Neal, H. Gordon (Box 51, Folder 1333)
      - Parker, Richard I.S., 1937 (Box 51, Folder 1334)
      - Perkins, Kenneth D., 1932 (Box 51, Folder 1335)
      - Robinson, Eric M., 1934 (Box 51, Folder 1336)
      - Turner, George R., 1932 (Box 51, Folder 1337)
      - Underhill, Gardner D., 1931 (Box 51, Folder 1338)
      - Wiggins, Verne, 1933 (Box 51, Folder 1339)
      - Wilson, George, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 1340)
      - Witmer, Frederic, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 1341)
  - Students, 1920-1929
    - Matriculated Students
      - Burroughs, Nelson M., 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1342)
      - Clark, Hugh S. (Box 52, Folder 1343)
      - Creamer, Francis B., 1924 (Box 52, Folder 1344)
      - Dare, Norman P., 1926 (Box 52, Folder 1345)
      - Fitzgerald, George L., 1927 (Box 52, Folder 1346)
      - Graham, Loyal Y. III, 1921 (Box 52, Folder 1347)
      - Paulsen, John, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1348)
      - Richardson, Arthur, 1926 (Box 52, Folder 1349)
      - Sasse, Louis, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1350)
      - Townsend, John H. Jr., 1922 (Box 52, Folder 1351)
  - Students, pre-1920
    - Matriculated Students
      - Cline, Thomas S., 1905 (Box 52, Folder 1352)
      - Gooden, Robert B., 1904 (Box 52, Folder 1353)
      - Harriman, C. Jarvis, 1908 (Box 52, Folder 1354)
      - Miller, Kenneth O. (Box 52, Folder 1355)
      - Rhea, Frank A., 1915 (Box 52, Folder 1356)
      - Roberts, Paul, 1912 (Box 52, Folder 1357)
      - Sasaki, M.J., 1916 (Box 52, Folder 1358)
      - Walker, John W., 1905 (Box 52, Folder 1359)
      - Wallace, Sidney W. (Box 52, Folder 1360)
      - Yamazaki, John M., 1913 (Box 52, Folder 1361)
  - Students, Pre-WW II
    - Matriculated Students
      - Conder, Evert (Box 52, Folder 1362)
      - Donegan, Horace W.B. (Box 52, Folder 1363)
      - Galaty, Gordon B. (Box 52, Folder 1364)
      - Knight, John (Box 52, Folder 1365)
      - Ladd, Edward T. (Box 52, Folder 1366)
      - Lund, G. Clarence (Box 59, Folder 120)
      - Mattocks, Henry (Box 52, Folder 1367)
      - Minton, Chester G. (Box 52, Folder 1368)
      - Platt, Donald O. (Box 52, Folder 1369)
      - Pryor, Francis J. III (Box 52, Folder 1370)
      - Ruetz, Franklin J. Jr. (Box 52, Folder 1371)
      - Sherman, Arthur M. Jr. (Box 52, Folder 1372)
      - Snoxell, W. Eugene (Box 52, Folder 1373)
      - Squires, Frank (Box 52, Folder 1374)
      - Wilson, Clyde (Box 52, Folder 1375)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Lists of Students, 1951-1971 (Box 52)
- Alumni, Series V
  - Alumni Fund
    - Reports (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Communication (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - St. Luke's Club
    - Letters, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Letters, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Letters, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Listings
    - Class Lists, 1904-1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Bishops, 1856-1918 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Directories, 1987-1989 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Directories, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Directories, 1970-1981 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Directories, 1942-1963 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Deaths, 1923-1950 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Deaths, 1969-1990 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Survey of Non-Ordained Alumni
    - By year of graduation, 1972-1974 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - By year of graduation, 1975-1978 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - By year of graduation, 1979-1981 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association
    - Newsletters, 1908-1985 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Constitution By-Laws (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Minutes (bound volume), 1916-1957 (Box 57)
    - Minutes (bound volume), 1902-1925, 1938 (Box 57)
    - Minutes, 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1969-1990 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Ledger (bound volume), 1959-1961 (Box 57)
  - Convocation and Reunions
    - Programs and documentation, 1922-1958 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Programs and documentation, 1971-1985 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Communications
    - Dean's letters, 1969-1974 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Dean's letters, 1975- (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Association letters, 1936, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Association letters, 1960-1975 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Association letters, 1987-1990 (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Academics School Life, Series VI
  - School Polity
    - Berkeley Center Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 146)
    - Berkeley Center Committee, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 147)
    - Berkeley Center Committee, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 148)
    - Berkeley Center Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 149)
    - Berkeley Community Senate, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 150)
    - Berkeley Community Senate, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 151)
    - Berkeley Community Senate, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 152)
    - Berkeley Community meetings, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 153)
    - Berkeley Association, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 154)
    - Berkeley By-Laws, 1977, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Grievance Board, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - BDS Mission Statement, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Student petitions, 1948-1969 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Committees
    - Christian Education Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Community Life, 1981-1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1972-1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Education, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Faculty, 1972-1981 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Faculty, 1975-1982 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Committee On Faculty, Colin Williams - Chair, 1972-1975 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Subcommittee for Clinical Appointments, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Subcommittee for Clinical Courses, 1972-1977 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Subcommittee on Faculty, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Subcommittee on Dobihal appointment, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Subcommittee on Special Lectureships, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Non-Ordinands Committee, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Orientation, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Personnel Committee, 1972-1983 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Professional Identity Committee, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Professional Studies Committee, 1972-1980 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Committee on Public Events, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Tripartite Committee, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - YDS Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - South Africa Divestment, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Self-Study / Accreditation
    - Berkeley's Mission, 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Feasibility Study, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Episcopal Study Committee on Preparation for Ministry, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Episcopal Study Committee On Preparation For Ministry - BDS/YDS, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Evaluations of Yale Berkeley under the Affiliation, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - ATS Visiting Team, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Board of Theological Education - Pusey Report, 1965-1974 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - YDS Self Study, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Proposals for Development, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - BDS - AATS Accreditation, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1981 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Admissions and Policies
    - General School Information, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - General School Information, 1971-1981 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Student Enrollment Figures, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - BDS Statistics, 1970-1990 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - Student Grades / Class Standing, 1957-1970 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - Degree Problems, 1971-1977 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - Registrar Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Pastoral Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Forms, 1971-1983 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Grading Policies, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1984 (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1981 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Admissions, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Admissions, 1981-1984 (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - Lists - Faculty, Students, Committees, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - Denominational Advisors, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - Donegan Award for Scripture and Liturgical Reading, 1965-1985 (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - Admissions to Ministry Pamphlet, no date (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - Society for the Increase in Ministry (SIM) Grants, 1953-1957 (Box 61, Folder 57)
  - Academic Programs
    - Course Grants / Funding
      - Trinity Church Grants, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 58)
      - Trinity Church Grants - Black Students Program, 1975-1978 (Box 61, Folder 59)
      - Trinity Church Grants - Black Students Program, 1972-1975 (Box 61, Folder 60)
      - The Hazen Foundation - Program in Theology Drama, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Course Evaluations
      - Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 62)
    - Academic Degrees
      - Berkeley Diplomas, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 63)
      - MAR (Masters of Arts in Religion), 1981 (Box 61, Folder 64)
      - M.Div. (Master of Divinity) / D.Min. (Doctor of Ministry), 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 65)
      - D.Min. (Doctor of Ministry), 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 66)
      - D.Min. (Doctor of Ministry), 1971 (Box 61, Folder 67)
      - Th.D. (Doctor of Theology), 1972 (Box 61, Folder 68)
    - Calendars / Schedules
      - Academic Calendars, 1958-1971 (Box 61, Folder 69)
      - Class Schedules, 1967-1980 (Box 61, Folder 70-72)
    - Course Areas
      - Area IV Courses, 1974-1978 (Box 61, Folder 73)
    - Anglican Core Classes
      - Anglican Formation and "Core" Courses, no date (Box 61, Folder 74)
      - Anglican Formation Program, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 75)
      - Anglican Core Courses, 1982-1985 (Box 61, Folder 76)
      - Episcopal Courses at YDS, 1979-1983 (Box 61, Folder 77)
    - Liturgical Offerings
      - Liturgy Courses and Programs, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 78)
    - Specific Courses
      - Black Religion, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 79)
      - Church History, no date (Box 62, Folder 80, 83, 85)
      - American Church History, 1934 (Box 62, Folder 81)
      - English Church History, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 82)
      - Patristics (Church History to the Council of Nicea) (Box 62, Folder 83)
      - Course from early 1900s (Box 62, Folder 86)
      - Criminal Justice Course, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 87)
      - Drama and Theology, 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 88-89)
      - Ethical Implication in the Biomedical Revolution, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 90)
      - Feminist Perspective Course, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 91)
      - Ministry Formation Retreat, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 92)
      - Monday Afternoon Discussion Group, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 93)
      - Moral Theology, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 94)
      - Pastoral Theology, 1948-1953 (Box 62, Folder 95)
      - Polity (Anglican/Episcopal), 1982-1996 (Box 62, Folder 96-101)
      - Prayer Book, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 102)
      - Prayer Book (Dean William Palmer Ladd), no date (Box 62, Folder 103)
      - St. John's Gospel, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 104)
      - Senior Seminar, 1996, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 105-106)
      - Spirit of Anglicanism, 1979-1998 (Box 62, Folder 107-116)
      - Systems Analysis Course, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 117)
      - Parish Development Course, 1983-1985 (Box 62, Folder 118)
      - Organizational Development Course, 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 119)
      - Papers Submitted to Prof. Lansing R. Hicks, 1976-1984 (Box 62, Folder 120)
    - Programs
      - Program Proposals, 1971-1993 (Box 62, Folder 121-123)
      - Air Force Chaplains, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 124)
      - Arts and Religion Program, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 125)
      - Black Studies Program, 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 126)
      - Continuing Education, 1926, 1974, 1993-2000 (Box 62, Folder 127-131)
      - Coventry Project, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 132)
      - Gerontology Program, 1983-1986 (Box 63, Folder 133-134)
      - Human Rights Center, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 135)
      - Independent Study Program, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 136)
      - Institute of Sacred Music, 1974-1982 (Box 63, Folder 137)
      - Lay Ministries Project, 1976, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 138-139)
      - Lay Vocation Training Proposal, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 140)
      - The Learning Process Training, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 141)
      - McFaddin Fund / Mission in Samaria, 1978-1983 (Box 63, Folder 142-144)
      - MidWinter Alumni Reunions, 1932-1950 (Box 63, Folder 145-146)
      - Mission and Ministry Program, 1978-1983 (Box 63, Folder 147)
      - Pastoral Care Program, 1972-1975 (Box 63, Folder 148)
      - Programs for Mission, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 149)
      - Professional Training Program Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 150)
      - Profiles in Ministry Program, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 151)
      - Religion and the Arts, 1971-1982 (Box 63, Folder 152-154)
      - Religious Ministries Yale New Haven Hospital, 1972-1976 (Box 63, Folder 155)
      - Roland Allen Forum, 1993-1998 (Box 63, Folder 156-158)
      - Sensitivity Training, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 159)
      - South African Education Program, 1981-1986 (Box 63, Folder 160-161)
      - Special Students, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 162)
      - Spiritual Direction / Annand Program, 1990-1992 (Box 63, Folder 163-164)
      - Spiritual Direction, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 165-166)
      - Spirituality Study Center, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 167)
      - Urban Ministries Program, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 168)
      - Vietnam Project, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 169)
      - Wartime Summer School, 1942-1943 (Box 63, Folder 170)
      - Westcott House Cambridge, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 171)
      - Women's Studies Program, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 172)
      - Working Group on Seminary Teaching, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 173)
    - Field Education
      - Clinical Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 174)
      - Consultation of Field Education Program, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 175)
      - Core Group Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 176)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 177)
      - Evaluation Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 178)
      - Descriptive Material, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 179)
      - Goals for Field Education, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 180)
      - Evaluation Questionnaire, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 181)
      - Lay Teams, no date (Box 64, Folder 182)
      - Field Based Courses, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 183-187)
      - Field Based Instructors, 1973-1982 (Box 64, Folder 188-189)
      - Field Education Program, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 90)
      - Field Education Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 64, Folder 191)
      - Grants Program in Theological Education, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 192)
      - The Growing Edge, no date (Box 64, Folder 193)
      - Inter-Seminary Theological Education for Ministry, 1971-1976 (Box 64, Folder 194-198)
      - Legal Assistance Program, 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 199)
      - Field Work Program Information, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 200)
      - Field Education Program Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 201)
      - Program Evaluations, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 202)
      - Field Education Supervisors Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 64, Folder 203-206)
      - Field Education Supervisors Newsletter, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 207)